INES RADIC

WEB DEVELOPER

Web developer with extensive knowledge in front and back-end development. University of Oregon graduate with a bachelor's degree in General Science and currently enrolled in the university's Full Stack Web Development Coding Bootcamp. I have newly developed skills in Javascript, CSS, HTML, and responsive web design using frameworks such as Bootstrap and Materialize. Known as a highly motivated individual, I bring forth great communication skills with my extensive customer service experience, understanding of user needs with my marketing background, and overall passion for front-end development. I am excited to apply my skills and experience to a driven team and further my knowledge in web development.

Links







LinkedIn: ines-radic

GitHub

Portfolio

PROJECTS

Music Spider | GitHub | Website

Summary: Using two APIs, the user can search parts of lyrics and the results will be the name of the artist and image, song name, link to lyrics, and three similar artists.

Role: CSS styling, responsive design, and Shazam API

functionality.

Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, API, Materialize

Weather Dashboard | GitHub | Website

Summary: Weather application that provides the current conditions for the user's searched city and the five-day forecast.

Role: Sole author

Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, API, Materialize

Better Books | GitHub | Website

Summary: Book application that lets the user save a list

of books for future reading. Role: Front-end development

Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Materialize, Sequelize, Google Books, Node, Express, & MySQL

EXPERIENCE

Roseland Theater **Marketing Assistant**

2019-2020 Portland, OR

Assembled expense reports and invoices for concerts, managed social media presence, advertised upcoming shows, and reported ticket sales.

Key Accomplishments:

• Handled calendar for upcoming shows as well as communicated with agents after just 4 months with the theater.

Sunglass Hut Key Holder

2017-2019 Portland, OR

Provided exceptional customer service, handled transactions, deposited and calculated daily sales reports.

Key Accomplishments:

• Promoted from sales associate to key-holder after 5 months with the company.

EDUCATION

University of Oregon

2020-current

Portland, OR | Certificate, Full Stack Web Development

University of Oregon

2014-2018

Eugene, OR | Bachelor of Science, General Science

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, CSS3, HTML5

Applications: GitHub

Tools: Node, ¡Query, Bootstrap, Materialize, API